Good morning.
Now, if you didn't know about my album Truth Translator, now you do.
You see, I understand that many of you who ask me to collab do so for news stories.
It is imperative that you also prioritize highlighting and platforming art and artists who highlight and platform what we actually need to do in terms of spiritual reset, mindful reset, decolonization reset in order to carry out the actions needed to change.
And the way that we want to see change.
Artists who use their creativity and their artistry to translate the truth that you are sharing in your medium through theirs.
Rasa, Rasa, you will rise.
Parallel sign will never die.
Forceding brought me back to...
So I formally request that all who hold themselves to leftist, radical, decolonization values also hold themselves to the charge of platforming and amplifying art that does the same.
Because it is no secret that art is an integral part of movement making.
And I am making movement music.
And I expect those about movement to support it.
But the problems where the board members sit, executives, a ruling class that laughs in cat system.
For artists, our work is our work.
You may think that the work that you're doing, organizing, nursing, child care, parenting, etc. is valuable because it is.
So is ours.
When we create, please make it your business to engage with it.
We engage with you in what is carrying you.
Engage with us in what is carrying us.
I got people I speak to every day who haven't taken the time to listen to my album.
It's 30 minutes long.
In this cancer season, under this cancer moon, I am done with supporting everyone around me.
And it not being prioritized to do so for me.
Recreate Cuba Libre Revolución
I got people I'm done with you.